Guide to the Rainbow Seniors of Western New York records, 2007-2007
Rainbow Seniors of Western New York records
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Rainbow Seniors of Western New York records, 2007-2007
7814
Rainbow Seniors of Western New York.
.3 cubic ft.
Organizational records and correspondence.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Records of the organization. Including board meeting and committee meeting minutes, bylaws, grants and correspondence.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Records of the organization. Including board meeting and committee meeting minutes, bylaws, grants and correspondence.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Rainbow Seniors of Western New York.
Subjects:
Gay men -- Societies and clubs -- New York (State) -- Rochester.; Lesbians -- Societies and clubs -- New York (State) -- Rochester.
Places:
New York (State) -- Rochester
INFORMATION FOR USERS
RELATED MATERIALS
Gay Alliance of the Genesee Valley records
NOTES
Arrangement and description of the Rainbow Seniors of Western New York records, #7814 made possible in part by a grant from the Documentary Heritage Program of the New York State Archives, a program of the State Education Department
CONTAINER LIST
- Bylaws, 2007-2009 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Minutes, 2007-2009 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Committees, 2008-2009 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Board Meeting, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Grants, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Finances, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Articles, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Correspondence, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Retreats, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  Mainly evaluation forms
- Surveys, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Advertising, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Membership List, c.2008 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Empire State Pride Agenda, 2006-2009 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Services and Advocacy for Gay Lesbian and Transgender Elders (SAGE), 2009 (Box 1, Folder 14)